Finding Aid for Penn Central Transportation Company Records 1835-1981
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Pennsylvania Railroad Company, 1847-1966; 83 linear feet
  - Superintendent-Toledo Division
    - Locality Files
      - Ohio
        - Toledo
          - Harding Memorial Bridge, Proposed, 1924 (Box 193)
          - High Level Bridge Over Maumee River at North Toledo: Proposed Construction by Eugene Rheinfrank, 1930; 2 folders (Box 193)
          - Magnolia Street Yard: Retirement of Tracks, 1937 (Box 193)
          - Manhattan Junction
            - Interlocker, 1925-1933 (Box 193)
            - Remote Control of Switches, 1929-1937 (scattered) (Box 193)
          - Maumee River Bridge
            - 1925-1927 (Box 193)
            - 1929-1931 (Box 193)
          - Michigan Belt Connection: Retirement of Track, 1936-1937 (Box 194)
          - Outer Yard
            - Passenger Station Platform, 1927-1929 (Box 194)
            - Proposed Enlargement, 1927-1928 (Box 194)
            - Proposed Floodlighting, 1925-1929 (Box 194)
            - Retirement of Crossover Near Ash Pits, 1931-1936 (Box 194)
            - Retirement of Boiler Shop and Storehouse, 1935-1937 (Box 194)
            - Retirement of Labor Camp Buildings, 1936-1939 (Box 194)
            - Retirement of Storehouse, Blacksmith and Boiler Shop, and Paint Shop, 1937-1940 (Box 194)
            - Retirement of Tracks, 1931-1936 (Box 194)
        - Vernon
          - Interlocking Plant
            - 1917-1938 (scattered) (Box 194)
            - 1929-1930 (Box 194)
        - Walbridge
          - Interlocking Plant
            - 1926-1929 (Box 194)
            - 1930-1936 (Box 194)
          - Interlocking Tower
            - 1925-1937 (Box 194)
            - 1939 (Box 194)
    - Subject Files
      - Bridges
        - Clearance Diagram, 1923-1931 (Box 194)
        - Speed Restrictions, 1919-1931 (Box 194)
      - Buildings to be Abandoned, 1928-1938 (Box 194)
      - Drawbridge Protection Studies, 1929-1930 (Box 194)
      - Grade Crossings on State Highways, 1928-1949 (scattered) (Box 194)
      - Livestock Pens, 1920-1924 (Box 194)
      - Maps, 1919-1938 (scattered) (Box 194)
      - Real Estate Department, 1925-1938 (Box 194)
      - Signals
        - Automatic Signal Installation
          - Carleton to Ecorse Junction, Michigan, 1929 (Box 194)
          - Main Line, 1925-1931 (Box 194)
          - Pere Marquette Railway, 1926 (Box 195)
        - Automatic Train Control Devices
          - Installation, 1922-1937 (Box 195)
          - Installation by New York Central Railroad, 1926-1928 (Box 195)
          - Miscellaneous, 1927 (Box 195)
        - Cab Signal Installation, Pittsburgh to Chicago, 1938 (Box 195)
        - Cab Signal Rules, 1932-1937 (Box 195)
        - Instructions for Code System of Continuous Train Control, 1927-1938 (Box 195)
        - Instructions to Signalmen on Manual Operation of Switches, 1933 (Box 195)
        - Plans and Specifications, 1920-1932; 2 folders (Box 195)
        - Report of Block Signal and Train Order Statistics for Interstate Commerce Commission, 1924-1931 (Box 195)
        - Tower signs for Block Stations, 1925-1933 (Box 195)
        - Valuation of Property and Valuation Maps, 1920-1932 (Box 195)
        - Value Sections, 1920-1929 (Box 195)
        - Water Facilities: Survey, 1930-1931 (Box 195)
        - Yards: Capacity, 1924; 1926-1938 (Box 195)
  - Vice-President and General Counsel (Legal Department)
    - Car Ferry Files
      - Agreements with Grand Trunk Western Railroad Company, October 28, 1931 (Box 195)
      - Agreements with Grand Trunk Western Railroad Company and Grand Trunk Milwaukee Car Ferry Company, 1935-1936 (Box 195)
      - Correspondence
        - September 1930-July 1933, 7 folders (Box 195)
        - August 1933-November 1935, 2 folders (Box 196)
        - February 1936-February 1938, 2 folders (Box 196)
      - Correspondence and Exhibits, 1932-1936 (Box 196)
      - Exhibits, 2 folders (Box 196)
      - Finance Dockets
        - Number 9109
          - 1931 (Box 196)
          - 1932, 2 folders (Box 196)
          - 1933 (Box 196)
          - 1936 (Box 196)
        - Number 9110, 1931 (Box 196)
        - Number 9112, 1933 (Box 196)
        - Number 9826, 1933 (Box 196)
        - Number 10114, 1933 (Box 197)
        - Number 10856, 1935 (Box 197)
        - Numbers 9109-9110 (Box 197)
        - Numbers 9109-9112, 1932 (Box 197)
        - Numbers 9109 and 9111-9112, 1932; 2 folders (Box 197)
        - Numbers 9109-9110 and 9826, 1933 (Box 197)
      - Photographs (Box 197)
      - Preferred Vessel Mortgage, 1932 (Box 197)
      - Stenographer's Minutes (Before the Interstate Commerce Commission)
        - April 14-16, 1932 (Box 197)
        - September 26, 1932 (Box 197)
        - June 1-2, 1933 (Box 197)
    - Consolidation of Railroads
      - Application Before Interstate Commerce Commission (B&O, C&O, NYC, & PRR), October 1, 1931 (Box 197)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Adamson Act: Memoranda re Constitutionality Prepared Under Direction of Conference of Railroad Executives and Counsel, 1916 (Box 197)
      - Agreement with Ann Arbor Railroad Company, 1922 (Box 197)
      - Agreements with Pere Marquette Railway Company, 1921 (Box 197)
      - History of the Eastern Division of the Central Region, Pennsylvania Railroad Company, 1929 (Box 197)
      - Interstate Commerce Commission Docket: Youngstown and Suburban Railway Company Agreements with Pennsylvania Railroad Company, 1930 (Box 197)
      - Lease of Pennsylvania-Detroit Railroad Company, 1923 (Box 197)
      - Report: The Railroad Passenger Deficit Problem, 1956 (Box 197)
      - Supreme Court of Pennsylvania: Final Opinion in Pennsylvania Railroad Company v. Driscoll et al, 1939 (Box 197)
      - United States Railroad Labor Board: Statement of Position, Policy and Purpose of Pennsylvania Railroad Company in its Dealings with Employees, 1921 (Box 197)
      - Wisconsin and Michigan Transportation Company: Annual Reports to Interstate Commerce Commission, 1930-1931 (Box 197)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad Company: Subsidiaries
    Pennsylvania Railroad Company: Subsidiaries (boxes 198-247; 290) is the final subseries and contains minutes, ledgers, journals, annual reports, and, occasionally, correspondence of railroads in which the Pennsylvania held a majority interest. Of these, the richest files are those of the Grand Rapids and Indiana Railroad, incorporated in 1855, and the Mackinac Transportation Company. Records of the latter are concerned with the company's applications to the Interstate Commerce Commission to abandon car ferry service; some photographs are included.
    - Allegan and Southeastern Railroad Company
      - Journal, General, 1878-1934; 1 volumes (Box 198)
      - Ledger, General, 1878-1934; 1 volumes (Box 198)
      - Minutes: Board of Directors
        - 1878-1927, 1 volumes (Box 198)
        - 1920, 1923-1924; 1926-1928 (Box 198)
      - Minutes: Stockholders, 1920; 1928 (Box 198)
    - Bay View, Little Traverse, and Mackinac Railroad Company
      - Journal, General
        - 1879-1882 (Volume 76)
        - 1881-1888, 1 volumes (Box 199)
      - Ledger
        - General
          - April 1879-February 1882 (Volume 77)
          - March 1881-January 1888, 1 volumes (Box 199)
        - Stock
          - 1881-1882, 1 volumes (Box 199)
      - Minutes, 1879-1888; 1 volumes (Box 199)
    - Chicago, St. Louis and Pittsburgh Railroad Company
      - Annual Reports, 1883-1889; 1 volumes (Box 200)
    - Cincinnati and Fort Wayne Railroad Company
      - Journal, General
        - 1851-1881 (Volume 78)
        - February 1853-March 1866 (Volume 79)
      - Ledger, General
        - February 1853-March 1866 (Volume 80)
      - Minutes, 1853-1866 (Box 200)
        (See: Cincinnati, Richmond and Fort Wayne Railroad Company, Minutes, 1873-1902)
    - Cincinnati, Richmond and Fort Wayne Railroad Company
      - Annual Reports, 1875-1877; 1881; 1882; 1886; 1892 (Box 200)
      - Board of Directors Files, 1923-1928 (Box 200)
      - Cash Book, 1867-1884 (Volume 81)
      - Journal, General
        - 1866-1909 (Volume 82)
        - 1872-1878 (Volume 83)
        - 1878-1885 (Volume 84)
        - 1885-1897 (Volume 85)
      - Ledger, General
        - 1866-1909 (Volume 86)
        - 1872-1897 (Volume 87)
      - Minutes
        - July 1866-April 1873, 1 volumes (Box 200)
        - April 1873-April 1902, 1 volumes (Box 200)
        - March 1903-April 1928, 1 volumes (Box 200)
      - Reports to Interstate Commerce Commission (Box 202)
        - 1898-1910, 13 volumes (Box 202)
        - 1911-1927, 18 volumes (Box 203)
      - Reports to Public Service Commission of Indiana, 1916-1917; 1919-1922; 6 items (Box 203)
      - Secretary's Files, 1853-1927 (Box 203)
      - Stock Receipts, 1866-1882 (Box 203)
      - Stock Register, 1868-1927 (Volume 88)
    - Cleveland and Marietta Railway Company
      - Annual Reports, 1890-1901; 1903-1905 (Box 204)
    - Cleveland and Pittsburgh Railroad Company
      - Annual Reports
        - 1881-1899 (Box 204)
        - 1902-1905, 1968-1970; 1972-1973 (Box 204)
    - Detroit and Mackinac Railway Company
      - Reports to Interstate Commerce Commission
        - 1933-1945, 11 folders (Box 204)
        - 1948-1950, 2 folders (Box 205)
    - Detroit and Toledo Shore Line Railroad Company
      - Reports to Interstate Commerce Commission
        - 1933-1945, 1947; 10 folders (Box 205)
        - 1948-1954, 6 folders (Box 206)
    - Detroit Union Railroad Depot and Station Company
      - Annual Reports, 1896-1921 (Box 206)
      - Board Files
        - Agreement of Merger with Penndel Company, 1954 (Box 206)
        - Appointments and Resignations, 1927-1954 (Box 206)
        - Cash Reports, 1946-1954 (Box 206)
        - Correspondence, 1913 (Box 206)
        - Election Tallies, 1934-1954 (Box 206)
        - Income Statements, 1928-1953 (Box 206)
        - Miscellaneous, 1931 (Box 206)
    - Detroit Union Railroad, Depot and Station Company
      - Cash Book, 1897-1918 (Volume 89)
      - Journal, General
        - December 1879-September 1881, 1 volumes (Box 207)
        - May 1881-June 1885, 1 volumes (Box 207)
        - January 1883-December 1885, 1 volumes (Box 207)
        - January 1886-December 1888, 1 volumes (Box 207)
        - 1889-1897 (Volume 90)
        - 1897-1929 (Volume 91)
      - Ledger, General
        - 1879-1881, 1 volumes (Box 208)
        - 1881-1885, 1 volumes (Box 208)
        - 1883-1885, 1 volumes (Box 208)
        - 1884-1886, 1 volumes (Box 208)
        - 1886-1888, 1 volumes (Box 208)
        - 1889-1897 (Volume 92)
        - 1897-1951 (Volume 93)
      - Minutes
        - 1881-1909, 1 volumes (Box 209)
        - 1914-1954, 1 volumes (Box 209)
      - Reports to Interstate Commerce Commission
        - 1937-1943, 7 items (Box 209)
        - 1944-1954, 11 items (Box 210)
      - Reports to Michigan Board of Assessors
        - 1911-1918, 1946-1948; 11 items (Box 210)
      - Reports to Michigan Public Utilities Commission (Box 211)
        - 1919, 1922-1932; 12 items (Box 211)
        - 1933-1936, 4 volumes (Box 212)
      - Reports to Michigan Railroad Commission
        - 1914-1918, 1920-1921; 8 items (Box 212)
    - Detroit Western Transit and Junction Railroad Company
      - Minutes, 1881-1892; 1 volumes (Box 213)
    - Fort Street Union Depot Company
      - Board Dockets, 1943-1957 (Box 213)
      - Minutes, 1940-1963; 2 folders (Box 213)
      - Annual Report, 1947 (Box 213)
    - Grand Rapids and Fort Wayne Railroad Company
      - General Journal, 1857 (Box 213)
        (See: Grand Rapids and Indiana Railroad Company, Executive Committee Minutes, 1857-1860)
    - Grand Rapids and Indiana Railroad Company
      - Annual Reports
        - 1868-1887, 1 volumes (Box 213)
        - 1886-1895, 1 volumes (Box 213)
      - Cash Book
        - 1854-1860 (Volume 94)
        - 1858-1866 (Volume 95)
      - Correspondence, July 27, 1871 (Box 213)
      - Dockets: Court Cases
        - 1881-1896 (Volume 136)
        - 1894-1910 (Volume 137)
        - 1910-1915 (Volume 138)
        - 1915-1923 (Volume 139)
      - Journal, General
        - 1854-1866 (Volume 96)
        - 1870-1878 (Volume 97)
        - 1873-1878 (Volume 98)
        - 1878-1882 (Volume 99)
        - 1882-1885 (Volume 100)
        - 1885-1887 (Volume 101)
        - 1887-1889 (Volume 102)
        - 1889-1891 (Volume 103)
        - 1891-1893 (Volume 104)
        - 1893-1894 (Volume 105)
        - 1894-1901 (Volume 106)
        - 1905-1916 (Volume 140)
        - 1916-1924 (Volume 141)
      - Ledger, General
        - 1854-1866 (Volume 107)
        - 1870-1878 (Volume 108)
        - 1873-1882 (Volume 109)
        - 1883-1888 (Volume 110)
        - 1889-1892 (Volume 111)
        - 1893-1901 (Volume 123)
      - Minutes
        - 1854-1878 (Volume 113)
        - 1879-1891 (Volume 114)
        - 1891-1896 (Volume 115)
      - Minutes: Executive Committee
        - 1857-1860, 1 volumes (Box 213)
        - 1877-1896, 1 volumes (Box 213)
      - Stock Ledgers
        - 1854-1859 (Volume 135)
        - 1854-1860, 1 volumes (Box 215)
        - 1854-1874, 1 volumes (Box 215)
        - 1870-1896, 1 volumes (Box 215)
        - 1881-1896, 1 volumes (Box 216)
      - Stock Transfer Book
        - 1855-1872 (Volume 116)
        - 1855-1874, 1 volumes (Box 216)
      - Stock Transfer Journal, 1854-1860; 1 volumes (Box 216)
      - Stock Transfer Register
        - 1854-1855 (Volume 116)
        - 1854-1894 (Volume 118)
    - Grand Rapids and Indiana Railway Company
      - Annual Reports
        - 1896-1905, 1 volumes (Box 217)
        - 1905-1915, 1 volumes (Box 217)
        - 1914-1925, 1 volumes (Box 217)
        - 1926-1940, 1 volumes (Box 217)
      - Board of Directors' Files
        - B184, 1871 (Box 217)
        - B184/1
          - 1910, 1914; 1916 (Box 217)
          - 1934-1953 (Box 217)
        - B184/2, 1917-1952 (scattered) (Box 217)
        - B184/3-B184/5, 1903; 1906; 1918-1920 (Box 217)
        - B184/6, 1897-1899 (Box 217)
        - B184/7-B184/8, 1927-1953 (Box 217)
        - B184/9
          - 1923-1933 (Box 217)
          - 1935-1947 (Box 217)
        - B184/10
          - 1920-1935 (Box 217)
          - 1936-1953 (Box 217)
        - B184/11-B184/13, 1928-1929 (Box 218)
        - B184/14, 1916-1933 (scattered) (Box 218)
        - B184/15
          - 1924-1930 (Box 218)
          - 1930 (Box 218)
          - 1931-1945 (Box 218)
        - B184/16
          - 1921-1930 (Box 218)
          - 1931-1938 (Box 218)
          - 1939-1946 (Box 218)
          - 1947 (Box 218)
        - B184/17-B184/32, 1928-1952 (scattered) (Box 218)
        - B184/33-B184/100, 1919-1953 (scattered) (Box 218)
        - B184/101-B184/160, 1916-1925 (Box 218)
        - B184/161-B184/240, 1916-1925 (Box 218)
        - B184/241-B184/280, 1918-1953 (Box 218)
        - B184/281-B184/285, 1949; 1952-1953 (Box 218)
      - Interstate Commerce Commission Docket (Abandonment of Missaukee, Lake City and Veneer Branches), 1942-1943 (Box 218)
      - Journal, General
        - 1896-1898 (Volume 126)
        - 1898-1900 (Volume 127)
      - Maps: Abandonment of Lines
        (Separately Catalogued)
        - Jennings and Missaukee Branches, 1925
        - Missaukee Branch, 1930 (Box 43)
        - Walloon Lake Branch, 1927 (Box 43)
      - Minutes: Board of Directors
        - 1896-1905 (Volume 119)
        - 1896-1908 (Volume 120)
        - 1906-1910 (Volume 121)
        - 1909-1914 (Volume 122)
        - 1910-1914 (Volume 123)
        - 1914-1918 (Volume 124)
        - 1914-1918 (Volume 125)
        - 1918-1931, 1 volumes (Box 219)
        - 1932-1953, 1 volumes (Box 219)
      - Rates of Pay, 1917 (Box 219)
      - Reports to Indiana Public Service Commission
        - 1915-1922, 1936-1938; 13 items (Box 220)
        - 1941-1953, 13 items (Box 221)
      - Reports to Indiana Railroad Commission
        - 1905-1914, 10 items (Box 222)
      - Reports to Interstate Commerce Commission
        - 1898-1909, 12 items (Box 223)
        - 1910-1920, 14 items (Box 224)
        - 1921-1935, 15 items (Box 225)
      - Reports to Michigan Board of Assessors
        - 1902-1913, 13 items (Box 226)
        - 1914-1920, 7 items (Box 227)
      - Reports to Michigan Public Service Commission
        - 1941-1953, 13 items (Box 227)
          (in same volumes as Indiana Public Service Commission)
      - Reports to Michigan Public Utilities Commission
        - 1919-1922, 4 items (Box 227)
      - Reports to Michigan Railroad Commission
        - 1902-1906, 1908; 6 items (Box 227)
        - 1909-1918, 12 items (Box 228)
      - Stock Certificate Register, 1896-1918 (Box 268)
      - Stock Ledger, 1897-1926; 1 volumes (Box 229)
      - Stockholders, List of (Volume 128)
    - Grand Rapids and Mackinac Railroad Company
      - Cash Book, 1867-1958 (Box 229)
        (See: Grand Rapids and Indiana Railway Company, Minutes, Executive Committee, 1857-1960)
      - Journal, General (Box 229)
        (See: Grand Rapids and Indiana Railway Company, Minutes, Executive Committee, 1857-1860)
    - Grand Rapids, Greenville, and Alpena Railroad Company
      - Minutes
        - July-October 1872, 1 volumes (Box 229)
        - November-December 1872, 1 volumes (Box 229)
    - Grand Rapids, Greenville and Bay City Railroad Company
      - Minutes, July 1880-February 1881; 1 volumes (Box 230)
    - Grand Rapids, Indiana and Mackinac Railroad Company
      - Journal, General, 1881-1884; 1 volumes (Box 230)
      - Ledger, General, 1881-1884; 1 volumes (Box 230)
      - Minutes, 1881-1884; 1 volumes (Box 230)
    - Grand Rapids, Rockford and Greenville Railroad Company
      - Minutes, 1871-1872 (Box 230)
        (See: Grand Rapids, Greenville and Alpena Railroad Company, Minutes, July-October 1872)
    - Grand Trunk-Pennsylvania Transportation Company
      - Board Files, 1933-1937 (Box 230)
      - Minutes, 1932-1937; 1 volumes (Box 230)
    - Green Real Estate Company
      - Minutes, 1929-1960; 1 volumes (Box 230)
    - Lake Superior Transit Company
      - Board Files, 1871-1895 (Box 230)
      - Minutes: Executive Committee, 1878-1890; 1 volumes (Box 230)
    - Mackinac Transportation Company
      - Board Files, 1945-1958; 3 folders (Box 232)
      - General Counsel Files (re abandonment of line)
        - General
          - Car Ferry Chief Wawatam, 1962-1964; 2 folders (Box 232)
          - Correspondence, 1955-1964 (scattered) (Box 232)
          - Meetings of Owner Lines, 1961-1965 (Box 232)
          - Notes by Robert Bierma, 1965 (Box 232)
          - Reports on Economic Growth in Upper Peninsula and Northern Michigan, 1961-1964 (Box 232)
          - Supporting Papers, 1963-1964 (Box 232)
        - Finance Docket 22813
          - Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 232)
        - Finance Docket 22917
          - Applications to Interstate Commerce Commission, 1967 (Box 232)
          - Briefs and Exceptions, 1965 (Box 232)
          - Correspondence
            - June 1963-January 1964 (Box 232)
            - February-, March 18, 1964 (Box 232)
            - March 20-May 1964 (Box 232)
            - June-, August 19, 1964 (Box 232)
            - August 20-November 1964 (Box 232)
            - December 1964-January 5, 1965 (Box 232)
            - January 1965 (Box 233)
            - February-May 1965 (Box 233)
            - June-December 1965 (Box 233)
            - January 1966-August 1967 (Box 233)
            - September 1967-May 1970 (Box 233)
          - Exhibits (Box 233)
          - Interstate Commerce Commission Reports, 1965-1971 (Box 233)
          - Mechanical File, 1963-1964 (Box 233)
          - Miscellaneous, 1961-1965 (Box 233)
          - Photographs (Box 233)
          - Testimony and Exhibits, 1965 (Box 233)
        - Finance Docket 22990
          - Applications to Interstate Commerce Commission
            - 1961-1965 (Box 233)
            - July 1965 (Box 233)
          - Exhibits (Box 233)
        - Finance Docket 26303
          - Applications to Interstate Commerce Commission, 1970 (Box 233)
          - Brief of Protestants, January 17, 1972 (Box 233)
          - Correspondence
            - September 1968-August 1970 (Box 233)
            - April 1970-January 1971 (Box 233)
            - February-July 1971 (Box 233)
            - August 1971-April 1972 (Box 233)
            - May-December 1972 (Box 234)
            - February-December 1973 (Box 234)
            - January-October 1974 (Box 234)
            - November 1974-March 1976 (Box 234)
          - Exceptions, October 13, 1972 (Box 234)
          - Exhibits 1-98 and Miscellaneous, 6 folders (Box 234)
          - Miscellaneous, 1971-1974; 2 folders (Box 234)
          - Report and Order Permitting Abandonment, August 15, 1972 (Box 234)
      - Minutes
        - 1881-1927 (Box 234)
          volume 1
        - 1928-1944 (Box 234)
          volume 2
        - 1953-1979 (Box 290)
          volume 3
        - Index to volumes 1 and 2 (Box 234)
      - Reports to Interstate Commerce Commission, 1959-1960 (Box 234)
      - Sale or lease of floating equipment, 1936-1941 (Box 273)
      - Leasing vessels for ice breaking, 1941-1949 (Box 273)
      - Requisition of Chief Wawatom by War Shipping Administration, 1943-1945 (Box 273)
      - Operating statements, 1949-1951 (Box 273)
      - Miscellanea, 1961-1965 (Box 290)
    - Muskegon, Grand Rapids and Indiana Railroad Company
      - Board Papers, 1885-1918; 2 folders (Box 235)
      - Journal, General, 1886-1895 (Volume 129)
      - Ledger, General
        - 1866-1890 (Volume 130)
        - 1886-1917 (Volume 131)
      - Minutes, 1886-1918; 1 volumes (Box 235)
      - Reports to Interstate Commerce Commission
        - 1898-1902, 5 volumes (Box 235)
        - 1903-1917, 18 volumes (Box 236)
      - Reports to Michigan Board of Assessors
        - 1903-1917, 16 volumes (Box 237)
      - Reports to Michigan Railroad Commission
        - 1903-1906, 1909-1917; 14 volumes (Box 238)
    - Pittsburgh, Cincinnati and St. Louis Railway Company
      - Annual Reports
        - 1869-1873, 1875-1878 (Box 239)
        - 1879, 1887-1889 (Box 239)
    - Pittsburgh, Fort Wayne and Chicago Railway Company
      - Annual Reports
        - 1862, 1866-1867 (Box 239)
        - 1873, 1880-1885; 1901 (Box 239)
        - 1907, 1910-1914 (Box 239)
        - 1917-1918, 1920; 1924-1927; 1929; 1932-1933; 1941; 1951-1954; 1956 (Box 239)
    - St. Louis, Vandalia and Terre Haute Railroad Company
      - Annual Reports
        - 1870-1901, 1 volumes (Box 239)
        - 1902-1904 (Box 239)
    - Terre Haute and Indianapolis Railroad Company
      - Annual Reports, 1869-1877; 2 folders (Box 239)
    - Terre Haute and Peoria Railroad Company
      - Annual Reports, 1897-1910; 2 folders (Box 239)
    - Terre Haute and Richmond Railroad Company
      - Annual Reports, 1853-1864; 2 folders (Box 239)
    - Toledo, Peoria and Western Railway Company
      - Annual Reports
        - 1895, 1897-1905 (Box 239)
        - 1911-1918, 1923 (Box 239)
    - Toledo Terminal Railroad Company
      - Annual Reports, 1908-1925; 3 folders (Box 239)
      - Minutes: Board of Directors and Stockholders, 1914-1964; 5 folders (Box 240)
    - Traverse City, Leelenau, and Manistique Railroad Company
      - Reports to Interstate Commerce Commission
        - 1906-1912, 7 items (Box 240)
      - Reports to Michigan Board of Assessors
        - 1902, 1906-1908; 4 items (Box 240)
        - 1909-1914, 6 items (Box 241)
      - Reports to Michigan Commissioner of Railroads
        - 1906, 1908-1913; 1916; 9 items (Box 241)
    - Traverse City Railroad Company
      - Journal, General
        - 1871-1895, 1 volumes (Box 242)
        - 1872-1895 (Volume 132)
      - Ledger, General
        - 1871-1895, 1 volumes (Box 242)
        - 1872-1917 (Volume 133)
      - Ledger, Stock
        - 1873-1916, 1 volumes (Box 242)